Yeah, from different areas.
>> Oh, all right.
>> Uh earlier someone had asked a question
about physics and technology. I wanted
to go a little bit deeper regarding
that.
>> Yes.
>> I feel that I have a gift and one of my
highest excitements is seeing the
clarity and simplicity in connecting
quantum mechanics to like you were
saying earlier the macroscopic level as
human beings.
>> Yes.
So in the development of that uh you'd
also mentioned that classical physics is
sort of a hindrance that's preventing
our society developing
um into these other quantum mechanics
and principles that
>> well I never said it was a hindrance.
Well, we the construct of our society
hasn't yet allowed us to be open to the
idea
>> yes
>> of that and um I just wanted to know if
you could maybe clarify
in order to advance our understanding of
quantum mechanics and physics as it
relates to the macroscopic level. Do we
need to find additional ways of
measuring things such as
>> not so much you just need to understand
the difference between quantum coherence
and quantum decoherence.
That's it. Because quantum coherence
exists on a quantum level. But when
there are so many molecules that they
jostle each other and create chaos and
decoherence, it's that decoherence that
actually creates your classical physics
level.
>> Okay?
>> But if you can impose coherence on
something macroscopic, you will actually
render it back into a quantum behavior.
>> Okay? This is how our ships work. This
is how they travel from star to star in
the blink of an eye.
>> We impose a field on a macroscopic ship
that is representative in general
typically of quantum decoherence. All
the different chaos of all the different
molecules is creating such a jumble that
the decoherence creates what you
understand to be your classical physics,
your physical reality. But the idea is
that by imposing a field upon it of
quantum coherence, it becomes literally
like one giant quantum particle and thus
can behave as quantum particles do. It
can be both a particle and a wave. It
can tunnel. It can do all sorts of
things that quantum particles do. And by
imposing that on it, then it can behave
very differently than things do in the
macroscopic world.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. With
very clear to me. All right.
>> Um, the next thing
is I had a question about your
civilization and you guys as beings.
>> Yes.
>> Uh, what is your I guess as we would
perceive it visible spectrum as we can
only, you know, some people would see
energies and some people can see just
the visible color spectrum. Can you see
X-rays, microwaves?
>> Yes, if we wish to, we can. Okay.
>> We don't always, but if we wish to, we
can. And even beyond that.
>> Okay. And then the other thing is are
you guys subject or do you possess an
autonomic nervous system and are you
subject to the natural body or brain
drugs that we experience such as
serotonin, dopamine, oxytocin?
>> That doesn't affect us so much anymore
because we are in our evolutionary state
what you would call quasifysical.
>> Okay. Therefore, we are deriving
transformational energies directly from
the electromagnetic field and the
gravitic field rather than the idea of
what you would consider to be chemical
fields.
>> Okay. Um, one other thing actually two
other things I guess.
>> Oh. All right.
>> Uh, regarding relationships within your
civilization. Yes.
>> Do you guys have what we call pair
bonding or you uh
>> it can happen but it's not like we have
a ritual that says it must. So
>> we simply allow synchronicity to
demonstrate what is appropriate for any
given individuals at any given moment.
Our entire civilization runs on
synchronicity. We are exactly where we
need to be when we need to be there with
whom we need to be in whatever
relationship we need to be and we know
this. Therefore we can take advantage of
knowing that and treat the relationship
for what it is rather than assuming it
to be something it is not. Thus,
whatever happens is what naturally
happens as it unfolds. Whether there is
bonding for a while and then not or any
other variation of this idea, we really
don't know what the relationship is
until the end of the life.
>> Okay, makes sense.
>> Yes, absolutely. The other thing going a
little bit back to physics is our
perception of the passage of time. This
isn't a time travel question per se, but
we perceive it as the era of time. It's
always going forward towards something.
>> Are you guys able to experience that in
either direction?
>> Well, yes. And actually, sometimes so do
you. It's called deja vu.
>> Okay. Because you feel like you know
what's about to happen. Forward arrow.
Because you feel like it already has.
Backward arrow.
Okay. Simultaneously.
But yes, we can experience it way beyond
that.
>> Okay. Um, one other question. I don't
know if you can disclose this or not,
but I feel as though I will be a big
catalyst or someone who is instrumental
in bridging this gap between letting go
of the, you know, uh, classical physics
and embracing this further of
technology. Will I
>> All right. Well, that may be so if you
continue to follow your excitement,
you'll find out. Will I work with your
civilization or other civilizations
somehow?
>> You may have a high degree of
probability of working with other
civilizations on this. It is difficult
to say at this particular point in your
time frame whether or not it would be
specifically with us or with someone
else.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
Hello Bashar.
>> And you good day.
>> Um
I have two questions.
>> Yes. One is um
when or if
when will we um
have the technology to build our own
ships to go to space?
>> You mean aside from the ships you
already have?
>> Yes, like exploration ships so we can
colonize and different. Well, again you
will find that
the highest probability of open contact
as we have said will be between 2025 and
2033 and after 2033
there will be an acceleration of
interaction with other civilizations to
the point that again by 2050 at the
latest you will have some basic form of
ships that are similar to what you call
UFOs
and can go exploring and beyond that as
well. Beyond that year, of course.
>> Okay. Is it possible that other
civilizations will come before that? To
give us an idea,
>> I just told you between 2025 and 2033
will be the beginnings of open contact
and the sharing of information and
knowledge that will lead to your ability
to join the stellar society. And by
2050, you will have your own ships. You
will be a member of the Interstellar
Alliance, at least at the beginning of
it. and you will be able to go
exploring. That's what I just said.
>> Okay. Sorry.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. Um, the other thing is,
is it possible? Well, I know it is, but
>> are you asking is it probable?
>> Okay. Probable
>> because anything is possible, but it may
not always be probable or relevant.
>> Okay. Um,
will humans from Earth be able to go
um talk to each other from mind to mind
or
>> Yes. when you finally fall in love with
each other
because that's what telempathy is.
Remember, you're not reading each
other's minds. You're on the same
wavelength and you're having the same
thoughts at the same time. That's what
telempathy is. That's why when you see
people who are in love with each other,
who have a close bond with each other,
they finish each other's sentences, they
know what each other is thinking. It's
not because they're reading each other's
minds. It's because each mind is having
the same thoughts because they're on the
same frequency.
>> Yes. And um can we connect a computer a
mind to a computer?
>> Yes, you can. just as we do with our
ships because our ships are sensient and
actually a physical representation of
our higher minds and the pilots of the
ships are keyed specifically to the ship
and vice versa. So no one else but the
pilot can fly that ship because the ship
is a representation of the pilot's
higher mind and no one else's.
>> Well, thank you.
>> Yes.
>> Well, that's all.
In fact, as we have said, when you
finally understand how to construct
so-called computers that are sensient or
what you call artificially intelligent,
which is kind of a misnomer, you will
actually find out that you are
conversing with your own higher minds.
>> Hey Bashar,
>> how are you? Good day.
>> I want to talk to you about integrity.
>> You go right ahead.
>> I notice in my life that I sometimes
make agreements with other people.
>> Yes. usually around like um going to the
same event or doing the same thing or
planning something with somebody.
>> Yes.
>> And then by the time it gets there or
just somewhere along the road, yes.
>> It's no longer representative of my
highest excitement.
>> All right. And so how to use integrity
and work that way? Yes.
>> Is that your question?
>> Yes.
>> Do you let everyone know that might
happen? That that's the person you are?
>> No.
>> Then there you go. You're out of
integrity. All you have to do is say,
"Well, you know, I'm excited about doing
this right now, and if you're okay with
it, I may actually find that something
else excites me along the way, and I may
not show up." And if you're okay with
that, then we're okay. But if you're
not, then I will attract people who may
be okay with that.
>> Okay. So, will I naturally attract
>> It's all about what you communicate.
>> Okay. Will I naturally attract people
who are okay with that? Because I have
done that in the past. And I feel like
on the receiving end, people tend to not
trust me as much if I do that.
>> No, it's not about them not trusting
you. It's about them trusting that what
you've told them is true,
>> that you may not show up.
>> Okay?
>> So, if they have made a decision that
they would prefer to be with people who
will, then obviously it's not so much
that they don't trust you, it's just
that they're telling you we prefer to
interact with people who when they say
they will show up will show up. One or
the other is not right or wrong. It's
just a matter of clarity of explaining
to people that that's who you really
are. At the same time,
you may also, just to be sure, want to
investigate your own beliefs to make
sure that that pattern isn't happening
because of the fact that you have
negative beliefs that are creating that
behavior when it doesn't necessarily
have to happen.
>> Yeah. But as long as you are clear
within yourself and discerning within
yourself and honest within yourself that
the idea of simply following your
excitement will make it from time to
time that you may change your mind about
where you wish to be and people know
that then they can work with that one
way or the other.
The idea, however, also to take it a
step further is to understand that if
you are really staying within your
excitement, it will be easier when
you're truly in that vibration to know
what things you actually will show up
for. There won't be so much confusion or
change about that because you will be
making a decision from within the pure
definition of your excitement. And you
know that it will be a high probability
that you will actually
manifest what it is you said you would
manifest because the knowledge is coming
from that state of being as opposed to
being uncertain about it.
>> Got it?
>> Make sense?
>> Yeah, it does.
>> So, it's a self-correcting system if
you're actually coming from your
excitement.
>> It will allow you to be where you truly
need to be when you need to be there.
It's not even that you necessarily have
to think about it. You won't be diverted
if it's important for you to be there
because you recognize that it is
actually a representation of your
excitement to do so. Because again,
remember it's the organizing principle.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. So, just make sure you're not just
flatsom and jetsum floating around
because of uncertainty. Allow yourself
to know that it may straighten itself
out when you are truly centered and
making decisions from within the state
of being that is your excitement. And
again, there may still be some
fluctuation. And as long as you
communicate that with people and they
know who they're dealing with, then
that's fine because then it's their
choice to decide whether they want to
have a relationship with someone who
does that or not.
>> Yes.
>> Because remember, most of the
difficulties in your relationships
doesn't come from what is said. It comes
from what's not said.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. So, be clear about who you
are. Even if you will change, be clear
about who you are right now. Let people
know that. Then they can decide.
>> Yes.
>> Whether or not to invite you.
>> Great. And sometimes you will find they
don't necessarily even have to invite
you because if you actually are acting
from your excitement and it is relevant
for you to be where they are, you'll
just show up anyway without even knowing
they were going to be there. That's what
I mean when I'm saying our civilization
operates on pure synchronicity.
We don't ever have to ask anyone to be
anywhere. We just know that where we
need to be, all the people that also
need to be there will be there. And
that's it. That's how it works.
Does that help?
>> Very much. Thank you.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Thanks.
Have a good day.
>> Hello, Bashar.
>> Hi. I have two questions for you today.
>> Oh, question.
>> Yeah. So, the first one's going to be um
as a Las Vegas native.
Yeah. It's all in my heart. I just want
to know what's so special about Vegas.
What's so special about it?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, obviously it's a great focal point
for the idea of randomness.
>> Locking into different realities and
seeing what comes up.
>> Okay.
>> Right.
>> Yes. The spin of the wheel.
>> Mhm.
>> That there is no absolute future. That
it can change in an instant. It's
dynamic.
>> It's challenging.
>> Yes. It reveals the deep core of your
being and forces you to deal with it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> There you go.
>> Yes, sir.
>> It's a very strong energy to be in. A
very bold energy.
>> Yes. And it's our home.
>> Yes.
>> And so I feel um I feel very honored and
blessed to be here.
>> Oh. All right. Well, thank you for
adding your energy to it.
>> Yes. Thank you. Thank you for coming.
>> Well, I'm actually above Sedona, but
you're welcome.
>> Yep. Same. Same. Um, and then my other
question is I want to know what the
purpose of wisdom teeth are.
Probably to chew your food wisely.
It's different for different people.
>> Okay.
>> Different things symbolize different
things in different people.
But obviously since your people decided
to call them wisdom teeth, there's some
association to the idea of knowing
exactly
Well, I'll just put it this way. Don't
bite off more than you can chew.
>> Yeah,
>> that's wisdom.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> All right,
>> that was perfect.
>> Thank you.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
>> Thank you all.
Hello Bashar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> I have a question about the oversoul.
>> Yes.
>> It's this energy that houses different
um entities on different planes and
planets. Well, in a sense, yes. The
oversoul is in concept a combination of
a multitude of souls in various
experiences. Yeah.
>> So, for example, we might not be aware
of them, but they could be aware of our
existence.
>> Absolutely. They are.
>> Yes. And what is a way for us to
communicate with them more consciously?
>> Well, again, the basics. Acting on your
excitement will expand your senses and
allow you to tap into what you need to
tap into from whatever source you need
it. Whether you know it's coming from
the oversoul or not is actually
relatively irrelevant. But the idea is
you can know that you're always
receiving communion from the oversoul
and with the oversoul for whatever
information you need that will help
guide you because through the oversoul
comes down through the soul and through
the higher mind into the physical mind.
Yes.
>> Sure. But how can we communicate to
these different beings that are
essentially part of our soul family?
>> All right. Well, again, I'm saying you
are communicating with them.
>> You don't always have to be aware that
you are because sometimes being aware of
it will actually stop the process of the
information you're receiving from them.
But if you act on your highest
excitement without any expectation or
insistence on the outcome and you need
to know specifically need to consciously
know that you're interacting with
another aspect of your oversoul, you
will it'll be brought to your attention.
But more often than not, the information
that comes through those channels comes
through unobtrusively so as not to stop
the process of you using the information
in your life.
>> Okay, I understand. And um I understand
the importance of following your
excitement, but what about um what's the
purpose of experiences like the dark
night of the soul and this limbo state
where you don't feel a relationship to
>> well there can be many many different
purposes depending upon how many people
are experiencing it. But in general, one
of the ideas is many people on your
planet because of the belief systems
that they've bought into sometimes
attract to themselves the idea of great
negativity because it clarifies for them
in no uncertain terms the difference
between what they don't prefer and what
they do prefer. And if that's the only
thing that your belief system will allow
you to become clear about, then that's
the way people will do it.
>> So you have to experience this
negativity. you have to.
>> Okay,
>> I just said that that's what many people
do because they are confused because of
their belief systems as to how to
experience joy. So sometimes they will
give themselves the experience of
darkness because in great darkness it's
actually easier to see any light at all.
>> It's like the idea and the symbol of the
candle in the middle of a dark void.
It's very easy to see the tiny little
candle because there's no other light
around it. So it makes it easier to find
the light when you surround yourself
sometimes with darkness. That's just a
methodology that some people use.
>> So what are ways to get out of that
state?
>> Go to the light
>> now that you found it in the darkness.
>> Go to the light. Be aligned with that.
Act in ways that allow you to express
who you truly are. be in alignment with
your preferred vibration by acting on
your highest joy and knowing that
anything that needs to be revealed to
you that's out of alignment will be so
that you can identify it and let it go.
>> I see.
>> Yeah.
>> Remember your yin-yang symbol shows you
that always always in the darkness there
is always a spot of light and even in
the light there is always the
opportunity to experience the darkness.
>> It can go both ways. It's up to you to
choose what you prefer and just keep
choosing that. You have to validate the
darkness,
not make it something more than the
light, but when everything is equal,
then you can choose what you prefer
without invalidating what you don't
prefer.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> Um, what is your relationship to the
Earth right now from from the ship that
you're at?
>> Do you mean how high above the planet am
I?
>> Yes.
>> About 1,300 of your mile,
>> give or take.
All right, that's not bad. Do you exist
in um in a re how should I say this? Is
the ship visible for
>> not to you?
>> No,
>> not yet.
>> It can be sometimes, but generally not
to you, not yet. And I mean you meaning
all of you, not just you personally.
>> Okay. All right. I have this idea that
um I was in Sedona this summer and I
experienced something called our
photography. Yes.
>> Where you have your palm measured and uh
it kind of measures the energetical
field around you and colors.
>> Yes. Yes. We understand the concept
intensity.
>> So my idea was to create a room that's a
multi-ensory experience room where you
get your energy measured.
>> How exciting.
>> Yes. So it would um work in the way of
re transferring that energy through
aroma therapy and music therapy and 3D
projection mapping.
>> All wonderful permission slips. When
will you do this?
>> That's my question. When will be a good
time to do it? So people people open.
>> Now would be a good time to do it.
>> What's stopping you from doing it now?
>> I'm not sure if people are open to this
concept yet.
>> I beg your pardon.
>> Yeah. Have you forgotten the one-sided
coin concept?
>> I don't know that concept.
>> Oh, let me illuminate you.
>> Tell me.
>> If you have a gift to give that you're
excited to give,
that tells you there must be someone
waiting to receive it or you wouldn't be
excited about it. It's like saying there
can be a one-sided coin. I have the
head, but there's no tail. Not possible.
If you have the head, there is a tail.
If you have a gift, there is someone
waiting to receive it or you wouldn't be
excited about giving that thing. There
is no pointless creation. Do you
understand? Your excitement is exactly
who you are. And if you're saying
there's no one in your reality waiting
to receive what you have to give, you're
saying you're pointless and that doesn't
exist.
Does that make more sense?
>> Absolutely.
>> So now is a good time. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Thank you.